
------------ re-search - rezultati ------------

\listoverridecount0\ls18}{\listoverride\listid1174145191\listoverridecount0\ls19}{\listoverride\listid389303874\listoverridecount0\ls20}{\listoverride\listid1991404275\listoverridecount0\ls21}}{\info{\title NetBus v}{\author Carl-Fredrik Neikter}
\par }\pard \qc\sl240\slmult0\nowidctlpar\adjustright {\fs28 NetBus v.1.70}{\fs24 
\par }\pard \widctlpar\adjustright {\fs24 The program can be used as a nice remote administration tool, or just to have some fun with your friends on the net. The network must support TCP/IP.
\par NetBus consists of a server and a client-part. The server-part is the program which must be running on the computer you wish to administrate. The client-part is the program you use to connect to another computer.
\par To install the NetBus server, you just run Patch.exe, on the target computer. By default it installs itself in the system, so it starts automatically every time Windows starts. In the NetBus-client you address the target with IP-numbers or host-names.
\par Plans for the future is of course an even more powerful tool. Unfortunately, the time I can spend on developing NetBus is limited.
\par {\pntext\pard\plain\f3\cgrid \loch\af3\dbch\af0\hich\f3 \'b7\tab}}\pard \fi-283\li283\widctlpar{\*\pn \pnlvlblt\ilvl0\ls15\pnrnot0\pnf3\pnstart1\pnindent283\pnhang{\pntxtb \'b7}}\ls15\adjustright {\fs24 Find NetBus servers with the u
Redirect console applications I/O to a specified TCP-port (telnet the host at the specified port to interact with the application).
t want someone else to connect to it you can password protect it. To accomplish this you start the server with the parameter /pass:thepassword, or use the administration functions in NetBus.
\par You should perhaps test the functions in NetBus against yourself before you start using it with your friends, so you know what\rquote s happening (send text will, however, not work on yourself)! Your own machine can be addressed via \'94localhost\'94.
